A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Civic Engagement and Government Program, Office Files of Amy Brown FA1846
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Civic Engagement and Government Program, Office Files of Amy Brown
2007-2016
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
Brown, Amy
FA1846
6.84 Cubic Feet 18 document boxes: 18 letter size boxes
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at the RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files, and officers' papers were transferred to and accessioned by the RAC beginning in 2011.
This material was transferred to the RAC in 2021 in two different sets of records and was ingested by the RAC as Accession 2021:016 and Accession 2021:120.
Accessions continue as necessary.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Collection consists of two series.
Collection arrangement is as follows:
Series 1. General files, 2007-2015 Series 2. Grant files, 2008-2016
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the files Amy Brown created when she worked as a Program Officer at the Ford Foundation, focusing on programming for financial justice and for providing financial opportunities and protections to low and moderate-income and marginalized communities. Most of the records in the collection originate from Brown's position as a Program Officer in the Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, Financial Assets Unit. There are also some documents created by Brown when she was a Senior Program Officer in the Civic Engagement and Government Program which was her last position at the Foundation.
The collection is comprised of two series with the bulk of the collection's contents contained in the second series. The first series contains general files mostly concerning convenings and program strategy, and the second series contains grant files documenting grant approvals, related communications and support, and reporting. Grantees focused on issues regarding affordable financial services and products, debt, credit unions, predatory lending, financial savings, financial reform and regulation advocacy, and the impact of new technology on the financial marketplace among other topics.
In addition to the grant status reports (GSR), grant communication summaries, and Recommended Grant Actions records (RGA) in the grant files, there are also materials like correspondence, reports, meeting materials, notes, drafts, and articles found throughout the collection.
Ford Foundation; Consumer credit -- United States; Consumer protection; Credit unions; Financial services industry; Financial security; Immigrants; Saving and investment
- General files, 2007-2015; 1; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Files in the series primarily concern convenings and program strategy and evaluation for Amy Brown's work related to the Ford Foundation's programing for financial justice and providing financial opportunities and protections for low and moderate-income and marginalized communities. They were mostly created during Brown's position as a Program Officer in the Foundation's Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, Financial Assets Unit.
  Program strategy and evaluation records in the series include grantee surveys, initiative results, reports, and a Learning Memo. Other common material formats found in this series include correspondence, notes, and drafts.
  - Theory of Change – Andrea Anderson-Hamilton, Anderson Hamilton Consulting, 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - 2012 Initiative Results (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2012 Financial Products and Services (FPS) Monitoring Survey, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Financial Products and Services (FPS) 2013 Monitoring Survey Report: Presentation of Grantee Survey Responses (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Financial Products and Services (FPS) 2013 Monitoring Survey Report, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted – Open in 2025
  - 2013 results reporting, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 2014 Financial Products and Services (FPS) Monitoring Survey, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Restricted – Open in 2026
  - 2014 Learning Memo, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - OM presentations, 2011-2013 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ford Foundation Financial Assets Grantee Convenings - Products and policy, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Consumer Federation of America (CFA) - Ford Foundation grantees convening on automobile insurance, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Consumer Federation of America (CFA) - Ford Foundation grantees convening on life insurance, 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ford Foundation grantee convening on mobile technology for financial access and capability, 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Payday loans and small dollar credit (SDC) grantee convening, Chicago, Illinois, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - U.S. PIRG (United States Public Interest Research Group) Education Fund - Ford Foundation grantee learning convening on big data, New York City, New York, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Grantee evaluation convening, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - D2D (Doorways to Dreams) Fund grantee convening on emergency savings, Boston, Massachusetts, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    D2D (Doorways to Dreams) Fund is now called Commonwealth.
  - Ford Foundation Grantee Convening - Financial Justice and the National Conversation on Race, 2010-2015 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ford Foundation Grantee Convening - The Intersection of Worker Justice and Financial Justice, 2013-2015 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Grant files, 2008-2016; 2; 6.08 Cubic Feet 16 document boxes: 16 letter size boxes
  Series contains grant files Amy Brown created when she worked as a Program Officer in the Ford Foundation's Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, Financial Assets Unit and then closed or continued to manage as Senior Program Officer in the Foundation's Civic Engagement and Government Program. Files document the approval, support, and reporting of individuals grants. Reflecting Brown's program aims of financial justice and expanding financial opportunities and protections to low and moderate-income and marginalized communities, grants in the series focus on:
  - Promoting access to affordable and fair financial products and services - Addressing issues regarding debt including student debt for higher education, credit card debt, public utility debt, unfair credit reporting practices, and racial and class disparities around debt - Expanding access to credit unions - Protecting consumers from predatory lending - Protecting homeownership and access to housing - Encouraging financial savings and matched savings programs and promoting savings approaches like tax times savings - Research into how families manage their financial lives for its implications on policy and financial products design - Financial reform and regulation advocacy - Increasing staff and leadership diversity in Federal financial regulatory agencies - Addressing technology changes in the financial marketplace such as big data and its impact on consumers as well as utilizing new technological approaches like mobile banking
  Communities which grants in the series center include Latino, Black, and immigrant populations.
  Brown's grant files typically contain grant status reports (GSR), grantee communication summaries, and Recommended Grant Action records (RGA). A GSR includes the grant's grant number which is incorporated into the title of every grant file in the series when that information is provided. Grantee communication summaries describe discussions, phone calls, meetings, and site visits related to specific grants and have records of those communications and notes attached to them. An RGA includes the grant's request number which is incorporated into a scope note on each grant file in the series.
  Later records from 2015 to 2016 document the strategic shifts happening at the Ford Foundation during that time which changed Brown's role to Senior Program Officer in the Civic Engagement and Government Program. Some grants Brown had managed were transferred to her colleagues Leah Mayor and Anna Wadia during the transition while others she continued to monitor.
  Files in this series also contain other kinds of reports, correspondence, meeting materials, drafts, and articles.
  - The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) - General support (Grant No. 1070-0327-1), 2008-2011 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) d/b/a The Financial Innovations Center. The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) is now called the Financial Health Network.
    Request No. 109013
  - Neighborhood Economic Development Advocacy Project (NEDAP) - Multistate financial justice (Grant No. 1070-0279-2), 2008-2010 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Request No. 109024
    Neighborhood Economic Development Advocacy Project(NEDAP) changed its name to New Economy Project.
  - U.S. PIRG (United States Public Interest Research Group) Education Fund (Grant No. 1070-1306-1), 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Request No. 109119
  - Appleseed Foundation (Grant No. 1100-1136-0), 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Request No. 113517
  - Public Interest Projects - Americans for Financial Reform (AFR) (Grant No. 1105-0993), 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Request No. 112832
  - Behavioral Ideas Lab (Grant No. 1100-1107-0), 2010-2012 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Request No. 112305
    Behavioral Ideas Lab d/b/a ideas42.
  - The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) - General support (Grant No. 1100-1372-0), 2010-2012 (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
    Request No. 112823
  - The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) - 1st planning grant (Grant No. 1100-0409-0), 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Request No. 113015
  - The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) - Surveys (Grant No. 1100-1111-0), 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Request No. 112826
  - The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) - Policy (Grant No. 1100-0270), 2009-2011 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Request No. 112790
  - Center for Responsible Lending (CRL) (Grant No. 1100-0108), 2009-2010 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Request No. 112148
  - Consumer Federation of America (CFA), 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Request No. 112025
  - Demos: A Network for Ideas and Action (Grant No. 1100-0145-0), 2009-2011 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Request No. 112304
  - D2D (Doorways to Dreams) Fund (Grant No. 1100-0470-0), 2009-2011 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Request No. 113063
  - Mayor's Fund to Advance New York City - SaveNYC (Grant No. 1100-0256-0), 2009-2011 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Request No. 112156
  - National Consumer Law Center (NCLC) (Grant No. 1100-0261), 2009-2011 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Request No. 112797
  - National Council of La Raza (NCLR) - Latino Wealth Building Policy Project (Grant No. 1100-0403-0), 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    National Council of La Raza (NCLR) is now called UnidosUS.
    Request No. 112137
  - National League of Cities (NLCI) (Grant No. 1100-0573-0), 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Request No. 112141
  - Neighborhood Economic Development Advocacy Project (NEDAP) (Grant No. 1100-0357), 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Request No. 112824
  - National Federal of Community Development Credit Unions (NFCDCU) (Grant Nos. 1100-0112 and 1010-1611-0), 2008-2010 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Request No. 112140 and 109190
  - Neighborhood Economic Development Advocacy Project (NEDAP) - Multistate initiative (Grant No. 1100-1105-0), 2010-2012 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Request No. 112285
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - SaveNYC (Grant No. 1100-0364-0), 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Request No. 112282
  - The Leadership Conference Education Fund - Americans for Financial Reform (AFR) (Grant No. 1110-0244-0), 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Request No. 114474
  - Appleseed Foundation (Grant No. 1115-1005-0), 2011-2012 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Request No. 114572
  - The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) - Small dollar credit (SDC) research (Grant No. 1110-1334-0), 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Request No. 114562
  - Consumer Federation of America (CFA) (Grant No. 1115-0345-0), 2010-2012 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Request No. 115208
  - Center for Responsible Lending (CRL) (Grant No. 1110-0123-0), 2010-2012 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Request No. 114029
  - D2D (Doorways to Dreams) Fund (Grant No. 1110-0414-0), 2010-2013 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Request No. 114561
  - Greenlining Institute (Grant No. 1115-0964-0), 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    Request No. 114583
  - Innovations for Poverty Action (IPA) - Financial Products Innovation Fund (Grant No. 1110-0847-0), 2011-2013 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    Request No. 115539
  - Mayor's Fund to Advance New York City - Cities for Financial Empowerment (CFE) (Grant No. 1115-0331-0), 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    Request No. 112308
  - Mayor's Fund to Advance New York City - SaveNYC (Grant No. 1100-0137-0), 2010-2012 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    Request No. 114030
  - Mission Asset Fund (MAF) - Cestas Populares-Lending Circles impact and evaluation (Grant No. 1115-1100-0), 2010-2013 (Box 6, Folder 54-55)
    Request No. 114578
  - National Consumer Law Center (NCLC) - Reforming the Consumer Financial Services Marketplace (Grant No. 1110-0279-0), 2010-2013 (Box 6, Folder 56-57)
    Request No. 114032
  - National Council of La Raza (NCLR) - Latino Wealth Building Policy Project (Grant No. 1110-1099-0), 2011-2014 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    Request No. 114573
  - National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions (NFCDCU) (Grant No. 1100-0138-0), 2010-2013 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    Request No. 114031
  - National Training and Information Center (NTIC) - National People's Action (NPA), 2010-2012 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - National League of Cities (NLCI) (Grant No. 1110-0573-0), 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    Request No. 114566
  - Neighborhood Economic Development Advocacy Project (NEDAP) - Community Financial Justice Leadership Initiative (Grant No. 1110-0280-0), 2010-2013 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    Request No. 114035
  - New York University - Financial Access Initiative (FAI) (Grant No. 1110-0899-0), 2010-2013 (Box 7, Folder 63-64)
    Request No. 114580
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Center for Community Capital - SaveNYC evaluation (Grant No. 1110-0696-0), 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 65-66)
    Request No. 114564
  - U.S. PIRG (United States Public Interest Group) Education Fund (Grant No. 1110-0118-0), 2010-2012 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    Request No. 112312
  - The Leadership Conference Education Fund - Americans for Financial Reform (AFR) reserve fund (Grant No. 1120-2844-0), 2012-2016 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    Request No. 118732
    Restricted – Open in 2027
  - Appleseed Foundation (Grant No. 1120-2398-0), 2012-2014 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    Request No. 116371
  - Aspen Institute - AssetPlatform (Grant No. 1120-1591-0), 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    Request No. 114570
  - Behavioral Ideas Lab (Grant No. 1120-2518-0), 2012-2014 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    Request No. 116373
  - Center for Responsible Lending (CRL) (Grant No. 0120-6041-0), 2012-2014 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    Request No. 118437
  - Consumer Federation of America (CFA) (Grant No. 1120-1961-0), 2012-2014 (Box 8, Folder 73-74)
    Request No. 116497
  - Demos: A Network for Ideas and Action (Grant No. 1120-0131-0), 2011-2013 (Box 9, Folder 75-76)
    Request No. 116359
  - D2D (Doorways to Dreamers) Fund - Mobile apps for financial services (Grant No. 1120-1972-0), 2011-2013 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    Request No. 117302
  - New Economy Project - Multi-State Financial Justice Collaboration (Grant No. 1120-2519-0), 2012-2014 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    Request No. 116374
  - Greenlining Institute (Grant No. 1125-2276-0), 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    Request No. 116370
  - Hope Enterprise Corporation (Grant No. 1125-2499-0), 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    Request No. 118077
  - The Leadership Conference Education Fund - Americans for Financial Reform (AFR) (Grant No. 1120-1601-0), 2011-2014 (Box 9, Folder 81-82)
    Request No. 116361
  - Mayor's Fund to Advance New York City - SaveUSA evaluation (Grant No. 1120-1621), 2011-2014 (Box 10, Folder 83-84)
    Request No. 116981
  - National People's Action (NPA) - New Bottom Line (Grant No. 1120-2003-0), 2010-2014 (Box 10, Folder 85-86)
    Request No. 117223
  - New York University - Financial Access Initiative (FAI) (Grant No. 1120-2203-0) Part 1, 2012-2014 (Box 10, Folder 87-88)
    Request No. 116364
  - New York University - Financial Access Initiative (FAI) (Grant No. 1120-2203-0) Part 2, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - U.S. PIRG (United States Public Interest Research Group) Education Fund (Grant No. 1120-0132-0), 2011-2013 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    Request No. 116360
  - Washington University - Refund to Savings Initiative (Grant No. 1120-2202-0), 2012-2014 (Box 11, Folder 91-93)
    Request No. 116363
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) - Compass Principles (Grant No. 0120-6031-0), 2012-2014 (Box 12, Folder 94-95)
    Request No. 118438
  - National Consumer Law Center (NCLC) (Grant No. 0120-6187-0), 2012-2015 (Box 12, Folder 96-97)
    Request No. 118436
  - National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions (NFCDCU) (Grant No. 0120-6107-0), 2012-2015 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    Request No. 118439
  - Center for American Progress (CAP) - Education Debt Campaign (Grant No. 0130-0892-0), 2013-2015 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    Request No. 119416
  - Center for Responsible Lending (CRL) - Americans for Financial Reform (AFR) (Grant No. 0130-0826-0), 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 100-101)
    Request No. 120188
  - D2D (Doorways to Dreams) Fund (Grant No. 0130-0302-0), 2012-2015 (Box 13, Folder 102-103)
    Request No. 119411
  - Demos: A Network for Ideas and Action (Grant No. 0130-1389-0), 2013-2016 (Box 13, Folder 104-105)
    Request No. 119430
  - Filene Research Institute - Accessible Financial Services Incubator (Grant No. 0130-1099-0), 2013-2016 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    Request No. 119419
  - Greenlining Institute (Grant No. 0130-0714-0), 2013-2015 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    Request No. 119418
  - Hope Enterprise Corporation (Grant No. 0130-0647-0), 2013-2015 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    Request No. 119413
  - Innovations For Poverty Action (IPA) - Financial Products Innovation Fund (Grant No. 0130-0648-0), 2013-2015 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    Request No. 119415
  - Mission Asset Fund (MAF) - Lending Circles (Grant No. 0135-0984-0), 2013-2015 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    Request No. 119417
  - National League of Cities (NLCI) - Local Interventions for Financial Empowerment through Utility Payments (LIFT-UP) (Grant No. 0130-0423-0), 2011-2015 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    Request No. 119412
  - Neighborhood Economic Development Advocacy Project (NEDAP) - Community Financial Justice Initiative (Grant No. 0130-0408-0), 2013-2015 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    Request No. 119409
    Neighborhood Economic Development Advocacy Project (NEDAP) changed its name to New Economy Project.
  - National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions (NFCDCU) - Very low income consumers research (Grant No. 0135-1070-0), 2013-2014 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    Request No. 120186
  - New York University - Financial Access Initiative (FAI) Financial Diaries (Grant No. 0135-1214-0), 2013-2014 (Box 15, Folder 114)
    Request No. 120620
  - Robinson and Yu, 2013-2014 (Box 15, Folder 115)
    Request No. 120432
  - The Urban Institute (Grant No. 0130-0556-0), 2013-2015 (Box 15, Folder 116)
    Request No. 118958
  - U.S. PIRG (United States Public Interest Research Group) Education Fund (Grant No. 0130-1392-0), 2013-2016 (Box 15, Folder 117)
    Request No. 119432
  - Washington University - Emerge evaluation (Grant No. 0130-1250-0), 2013-2016 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    Request No. 119421
  - Ways to Work (Grant No. 0135-0160), 2013-2014 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    Request No. 120004
  - Center for Community Change (CCC) - Young Invincibles (YI), 2013-2014 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    Request No. 120383
  - U.S. PIRG (United States Public Interest Research Group) Education Fund - Consumer Financial Protection Program, 2015-2016 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    Request No. 124142
  - The Leadership Conference Education Fund - Americans for Financial Reform (AFR) (Grant No. 0140-0168-0), 2014-2015 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    Request No. 121820
  - Appleseed Foundation - Immigrant Financial Future Initiative (Grant No. 0140-0738-0), 2014-2016 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    Request No. 121831
  - Behavioral Ideas Lab - Designing Financial Products that Matter (Grant No. 0140-0776-0), 2014-2016 (Box 16, Folder 124)
    Request No. 121830
  - Center for American Progress (CAP) - Higher Ed. not Debt Campaign (Grant No. 0140-1313-0), 2014-2016 (Box 16, Folder 125)
    Request No. 121855
  - Center for Community Change (CCC) - Young Invincibles (YI) (Grant No. 0150-0267), 2015 (Box 16, Folder 126)
    Request No. 123478
  - The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) (Grant No. 0140-1097-0), 2014-2016 (Box 16, Folder 127)
    Request No. 121837
  - Consumer Federation of America (CFA) (Grant No. 0140-0392-0), 2014-2016 (Box 16, Folder 128)
    Request No. 121825
  - Center for Responsible Lending (CRL) (Grant No. 0140-1234-0), 2014-2016 (Box 16, Folder 129-130)
    Request No. 121852
  - Continuum - Institute of International Education (IIE) grant, 2014-2015 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - National Consumer Law Center (NCLC) (Grant No. 0140-1187-0), 2014-2016 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    Request No. 121858
  - National Council of La Raza (NCLR) - Latino Wealth Building Initiative (Grant No. 0140-0306-0), 2014-2015 (Box 17, Folder 133)
    Request No. 121822
  - National Federation of Community Development Credit Unions (NFCDCU) (Grant No. 0140-1224-0), 2014-2016 (Box 17, Folder 134)
    Request No. 121853
  - National People's Action (NPA) - Consumer Lending Coalition (Grant No. 0140-0363-0), 2014-2016 (Box 17, Folder 135)
    Request No. 121827
  - New York University - U.S. Financial Diaries research project (Grant No. 0140-1071-0), 2014-2016 (Box 17, Folder 136)
    Request No. 121835
  - Robinson and Yu, 2014-2015 (Box 17, Folder 137)
    Request No. 122786
  - Washington University - Refund to Savings (Grant No. 0140-0622-0), 2014-2016 (Box 17, Folder 138-139)
    Request No. 121832
  - Woodstock Institute - Multi-State Financial Justice Advocacy Collaboration (Grant No. 0140-0904-0), 2014-2016 (Box 17, Folder 140)
    Request No. 121834
  - Appleseed Foundation - Immigrant Financial Futures Initiative (Grant No. 0140-0738-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 141)
    Request No. 125428
  - The Conference Board - Community for Economic Development (CED) Sustainable Capitalism Project (Grant No. 0155-0661-0), 2014-2016 (Box 18, Folder 142)
    Request No. 125050
  - Consumer Federation of America (CFA), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 143)
    Request No. 123489
  - D2D (Doorways to Dreams) Fund (Grant No. 0150-0260-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 144)
    Request No. 123475
  - Greenlining Institute - Building Systems for Financial Equity (Grant No. 0150-0798-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 145)
    Request No. 124147
  - Hope Enterprise Corporation (Grant No. 0150-0615-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    Request No. 123480
  - Innovations for Poverty Action (IPA) - Financial Products Innovation Fund (Grant No. 0150-0745-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 147)
    Request No. 124150
  - Mission Asset Fund (MAF) (Grant No. 0155-0735-0), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 148)
    Request No. 124152
  - National Council of La Raza (NCLR) - Latino Wealth Building Initiative (Grant No. 0140-0306), 2015-2016 (Box 18, Folder 149)
    Request No. 123487